The delegation from the Animal Kingdom of Eurazania,
،الوفد القادم من مملكة الحيوان يورازانيا
sent by the Demon Lord Carrion, arrived in Tempest.
،والمُرسل من طرف سيّد الشّياطين كاريون وصل إلى تيمبيست
But the moment they did, some things happened...
...لكن في لحظة وصوله، حدثت بعض الأمور
And this is what it devolved into.
وهذا ما آلت إليه الأمور
I mean, it is kind of my fault... I guess?
أعني... أنّها غلطتي على ما أعتقد، صحيح؟
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
ذلك الوقت الذي خُلقت فيه من جديد كهُلام
Episode 26: Trade with the Animal Kingdom
الحلقة 26: تجارة مع مملكة الحيوان
Is that all the strength a Kijin has?
أهذه كلّ القوّة التي يملكها كيجين؟
You can entertain me a lot more than that!
!يمكنكِ أن تمتّعيني أكثر من ذلك
That was my intent all along.
كانت تلك نيّتي منذ البداية
Prepare yourself!
!حضّري نفسكِ
That's...
...هذه
A maximum Magic Bullet?!
!رصاصة سحر قصوى؟
H-Hey, Shion, hang on a second!
!شيون، انتظري لحظة
Do you wanna blow this entire area to bits?!
!أتريدين تدمير هذا المكان بأكمله
Oh, jeez! She's not listening!
!تبّاً! إنّها لا تصغي
Ooh, nice! Bring it on!
!عظيم! أنا جاهزة
And that Suphia lady is dead set on taking it!
!وتلك الآنسة صوفيا عازمة على تلقّيها
Will there even be anything left of her if that thing hits her?!
!هل سيبقى منها شيء حتّى إذا أصابتها هذه؟
What do I do? Stop her?
ماذا أفعل؟ أوقفها؟
Here it comes!
!ها أنا ذي
Stop!
!توقّفي
That is enough.
هذا يكفي
Beast transformation, huh?
تحوُّل وحش؟
Let us end this here.
لننهِ هذا الأمر هنا
So what's the verdict? Do we pass?
حسناً، ما القرار؟ هل نجحنا؟
Yes.
أجل
We're done here.
انتهينا هنا
Huh?
ماذا؟
Er, Master, does this mean...
...هل هذا يعني يا سيّدي
It looks like they were testing us.
يبدو أنّهم كانوا يختبروننا
No complaints here. Your might is impressive.
لا شكوى. قوّتكم مذهلة
There'll be plenty of value for us in associating with you as equals.
التعاون معكم كطرف متكافئ فيه فائدة كبيرة لنا
I'm convinced of that now.
أنا مقتنعة بذلك الآن
To underestimate the leader of the Jura Tempest Federation,
،التّقليل من شأن قائد اتّحاد جورا تيمبيست
Rimuru Tempest, and his companions
ريمورو تيمبيست، ومرافقيه
should be considered an insult to Lord Carrion!
!يُعدّ إهانة بحقّ كاريون-ساما
Got it?
مفهوم؟
Yes, ma'am!
!حاضر
Lady Suphia is right.
صوفيا-ساما على حقّ
There aren't many humans who can keep up with me so well.
قلّما تجد من البشر ممّن يستطيعون مجاراة قوّتي
Glad to hear that.
يسرّني سماع ذلك
They had me worried, and so soon after they arrived here...
...أقلقوني حقّاً، وبعد وصولهم إلى هنا مباشرة
I'm glad it all worked out nicely.
أنا مسرورة لأنّ الأمور سارت على ما يُرام
Shion, you get it now, right?
شيون، تفهمين الآن، صحيح؟
Shion?
شيون؟
Um...
...المعذرة
What do I do with this?
ماذا أفعل بهذه؟
Crap! It's about to blow!
!تبّاً! إنها على وشك أن تنفجر
C-Can't you get rid of it?!
!أ-ألا يمكنك التخلّص منها؟
No, I can't! My energy is at its limit!
!لا، لا أستطيع! بلغت طاقتي حدودها
Great Rimuru, we must take shelter.
ريمورو-ساما، يجب أن نبحث عن ملجأ
J-Just calm down!
!ا-اهدئي فحسب
Gently... Gently aim that thing upward!
!برفق... صوّبي برفق نحو الأعلى
U-Upward?
ا-الأعلى؟
Force it if you have to! Just do it!
!ادفعيها إذا اضطررتِ! افعليها فحسب
I-I don't think I can!
!لـ-لا أستطيع
Honestly, Shion, you're hopeless.
تبّاً يا شيون، كم أنتِ بائسة
Shion, fire it at me!
!شيون، أطلقيها نحوي
Don't worry.
لا تقلقي
But...
...لكن
Trust me!
!ثِقي بي
O-Okay! Here it comes!
!حـ-حسناً! ها هي ذي
Gluttony!
!شراهة
There, all done.
حسناً، انتهيت
It can't be...
...مستحيل
Are you kidding me?
أهذا معقول؟
That much is only natural to expect from my master.
هذا أمر طبيعي ومُتوقّع من مولايّ
Are you all right?
هل أنتِ بخير؟
I can see why Lord Carrion approves of you.
لهذا يشهد كاريون-ساما بك
We are grateful that our nation has established relations with yours.
نحن ممتنّون لأنّ بلدنا بنت علاقات مع بلدكم
Likewise.
كذلك نحن
Welcome to Tempest!
!مرحباً بكم في تيمبيست
Thus we welcomed the delegation from Eurazania.
وهكذا رحّبنا بالوفد القادم من يورازانيا
That night,
،في تلك اللّيلة
a little welcome party was held in the reception hall we had just completed.
أقيمت حفلة ترحيب بسيطة في صالة الاستقبال التي كنّا قد بنيناها مؤخّراً
This is good!
!هذا لذيذ
The flavoring is fantastic.
النّكهة ممتازة
It's just salty enough, too.
ملحه مثاليّ أيضاً
I could eat this forever!
!لا أشبع من هذا مهما أكلت
Delicious!
!لذيذ
What bliss.
يا له من نعيم
She's quite the drinker.
إنّها مدمنة شرب حقّاً
Who the heck gave her entire barrels?
من أعطاها البراميل بأكملها بالضبط؟
And over here...
...وهنا
Hey, are you sure you should let strangers see you doing that?
هل أنتِ متأكّدة أنه لا مانع أن يراكِ الغُرباء تفعلين ذلك؟
It isn't particularly a secret.
هذا ليس سرّاً
R-Really?
حـ-حقّاً؟
But...
...لكن
it is a side I only show to those I trust.
إنّه جانب لا أظهره إلّا لِمن أثق بهم فقط
I see. Well, okay, then.
هكذا إذاً. حسناً
Still, though...
...لكن رغم ذلك
I can't believe you drank all of the apple brandy alone.
لا أصدّق أنّكِ شربتِ كلّ مشروب التفّاح الكحولي بمفردك
All of it?
كلّه؟
You don't make very much?
لا تصنعون الكثير؟
Oh, sorry. Don't worry about it.
آسف. لا تقلقي بشأن ذلك
Of course, it's something we make specially for guests,
،بالطبع، إنّه شيء نصنعه خصّيصاً للضيوف
but we rely on the bounty of the forest for our fruit,
،لكن نعتمد على خيرات الغابة لتوفير الفاكهة
so we can't pick very much.
لذا لا يمكننا قطف الكثير
In that case, I have a good idea.
في هذه الحالة، لديّ فكرة سديدة
Fruit is abundant in Eurazania.
الفواكه متاحة بوفرة في يورازانيا
I can arrange to have some sent here.
يمكنني طلب إحضار الفاكهة إلى هنا
What? Really?
ماذا؟ حقّاً؟
Of course.
بالطبع
Isn't that wonderful, Great Rimuru?
أليس هذا رائعاً يا ريمورو-ساما؟
Yeah!
!أجل
I see.
هكذا إذاً
That's a "so give us your country's booze," isn't it?
"كأنّني أسمع عبارة "لذا أعطونا خمراً من بلدكم
In what ratio?
ما النسبة؟
We'll trust you to work out the details.
سنثق بكم فيما يتعلّق بالتفاصيل
I'm happy as long as I can drink good liquor.
أنا سعيدة ما دمتُ أشرب شراباً لذيذاً
Eurazania's fruit is top-quality, so you can expect the best!
فاكهة يورازانيا بأعلى جودة، لذا يمكنكم أن تتوقّعوا شيئاً مثاليّاً
Leaving the mundane stuff to us, huh?
ترك الأعمال الروتينيّة على عاتقنا؟
How much would make it an equal trade?
أي تجارة متكافئة هي هذه؟
Okay. I'll let a specialist handle this.
حسناً. سأدع مختصّاً يعالج هذا الأمر
Shuna!
!شونا
Yes, Great Rimuru?
أمرك يا ريمورو-ساما؟
Go get Koby for me.
أحضري كوبي إليّ
He's a Kobold merchant.
إنّه تاجر كوبولد
Kobold Merchant  Koby
كوبي    تاجر كوبولد
He's running a shop in Tempest now,
،يفتتح متجراً في تيمبيست الآن
and he manages all of our merchants.
ويدير شؤون كلّ تجّارنا
G-Great Rimuru, what is this about?
ر-ريمورو-ساما، ما الأمر؟
This is Koby-chan. He represents all our merchants.
هذا كوبي-تشان. مُمثّل كافّة تجّارنا
He's also done business in Demon Lord domains,
،أدّى أعمالاً أيضاً في مناطق تابعة لسيّد الشّياطين
so I'm putting him in charge of our trade.
لهذا أعيّنه مسؤولاً عن تجارتنا
These folks are from the Animal Kingdom.
هذان من مملكة الحيوان
If there's anything besides the liquor that you're interested in, negotiate away.
إن كان هناك أي شيء آخر يجذب اهتمامكم غير المشروب، تفاوضوا عليه
Wait, wait, wait! Weaker races aren't allowed in the Animal Kingdom!
لحظة، لحظة، لحظة! لا يُسمح للأجناس الأضعف أن يدخلوا مملكة الحيوان
We'll make sure to get you clearance. Don't be shy.
سنحرص على حصول استثناء لك. لا تخجل
And we will inform Lord Carrion in advance.
وسنبلغ كاريون-ساما سلفاً
You're not all that different from the Lycanthropes.
أنت لا تختلف كثيراً عن المستذئبين
You'll get on fine.
ستكون أمورك بخير
What?!
!ماذا؟
So it's settled. Thanks!
!حُسم الأمر إذاً. شكراً
Um, er... All right...
...المعذرة... حسناً
Well, I'll leave you young folks to it, then.
حسناً، سأدع الأمر لكم إذاً
Please excuse us.
نستأذن بالانصراف
Huh?! Wha... Wait!
!ماذا؟!... لحظة
Great Rimuru!
!ريمورو-ساما
We can rest easy with Koby-chan handling it.
يمكننا أن نسلّم الأمر لكوبي-تشان مطمئنّين
Yes, you're right.
أجل، معك حقّ
Negotiations always go more smoothly over drinks, too.
المُفاوضات دائماً ما تسير بسلاسة أكبر على المشروبات أيضاً
And so the night wore on.
وهكذا مضت اللّيل
Not a bad start to our relations with foreign lands!
!بداية لا بأس بها لعلاقاتنا مع بلاد أجنبيّة
A few days later, Albis and Suphia returned to Eurazania.
بعد أيّام قليلة، عادت ألبيس وصوفيا إلى يورازانيا
Our nations plan to share our skills, as well.
يخطّط بلدانا لمشاركة مهاراتنا كذلك
These folks stayed behind in Tempest to learn some of our techniques.
بقي هؤلاء القوم في تيمبيست لتعلّم المزيد من تقنيّاتنا
They're all diligent and good-natured.
إنّهم مثابرون ولطيفون
How do you get hot water to come out of this thing you call a "faucet"?
كيف تدعون ماء ساخناً يخرج من هذا الشيء الذي تدعونه "صنبور"؟
You don't seem to be boiling it anywhere.
لا يبدو لي أنّكم تغلونه في مكان ما
It's rune magic.
إنّه سحر رونيّ
Rune magic?
سحر رونيّ؟
Where are the runes?
أين هي الرونيّات؟
There's a magicrystal with a heat magic rune on it built into the handle.
هناك بلّورة سحريّة عليها رونيّة سحريّة حراريّة مُنصّبة مع القبضة
I see!
!هكذا إذاً
So if anyone with magic turns it, the water is heated!
!لذا إذا دوّرها شخص بسحر، يتسخّن الماء
Dwarf artisans really know their stuff!
!الحِرفيّون الأقزام ماهرون حقّاً
Aw, this isn't such a big deal.
هذا ليس بالأمر الجلل
Plus it was actually Rimuru's idea...
...بالإضافة إلى أنّها كانت فكرة ريمورو
To be precise, it was Great Sage's idea.
بعبارة أدقّ، كانت فكرة الحكيم العظيم
You're not gonna observe the artisans like the rest of your people?
ألن تراقب الحِرفيّين كبقيّة قومك؟
Nah, not me.
لا، لستُ أنا
Sir Phobio, the Black Leopard Fang, who's in confinement now,
،فوبيو-ساما، ناب النّمر الأسود، والحبيس الآن
ordered me to be useful to Great Rimuru.
أمرني أن أكون مفيداً لريمورو-ساما
That's why you're hanging out with the town guard?
لهذا ترافق حرس البلدة؟
That's right.
أجل
Hey, Grucius!
!غريشيس
We're going on patrol.
سنخرج في دوريّة
Got it.
حسناً
Later.
إلى اللّقاء
Well, guess I'll hop in the bath or something...
...حسناً، أظنّني سأذهب للاستحمام
You will train with the sword.
ستتدرّب على السّيف
Yes, sir.
حاضر
For dividing fractions, looking at it this way is a bit difficult,
بالنسبة لكسور القسمة، النظر للأمر بهذه الطريقة صعب قليلاً
so we'll try converting them to multiplication problems.
لذا سنجرّب تحويلها إلى مسائل عمليّات ضرب حسابيّة
To convert division problems to multiplication problems,
،لتحويل مسائل القسمة إلى مسائل ضرب
They're still studying even without me here.
ما زالوا يدرسون حتّى من دوني هنا
you swap the numerator and denominator on the right side.
نبدّل ما بين البسط والمقام في الجانب الأيمن
We call this the inverse.
نُطلق على هذا بالمعكوس
When you multiply the inverse with the original number, the answer is always...
عندما نضرب المعكوس بالعدد الأصلي ...فإنّ الإجابة دوماً هي
Then a few more days passed...
ثمّ مضت بضعة أيّام
and Youm's gang set out to further spread their reputation as champions.
وعصابة يوم شدّت الرّحال لتنتشر سمعتها أكثر كأبطال
They just missed the return of our delegation led by Benimaru.
فاتهم فقط عودة وفدنا بقيادة بينيمارو
Eurazania's knights are as remarkable as you would expect.
فرسان يورازانيا جديرون بالإعجاب كما هي التوقّعات
Every last knight was painstakingly trained by Demon Lord Carrion himself.
كلّ فارس قد تلقّى تدريباً قاسياً على يد سيّد الشّياطين كاريون بنفسه
I can see why they call him the Beastmaster.
لهذا يطلقون عليه زعيم الوحوش
Anything else?
هل من شيء آخر؟
Yes. The buildings there are quite crude compared to Tempest's.
أجل. المباني هناك بدائيّة جدّاً مقارنة بمباني تيمبيست
But the royal palace is highly extravagant.
لكن القصر الملكيّ مُترف جدّاً
It's very clear that the wealth is concentrated there.
من الواضح أنّ الثّروة متركِّزة هناك
Rigur has grown into such a fine man!
!أصبح ريغور رجلاً حقيقيّاً
But I don't mean that in a bad way.
لكن لا أقصد ذلك بصورة سيّئة
It's what the kingdom's citizens want.
فهذا ما يريده مُواطنو المملكة
I see.
هكذا إذاً
And it's not just the architecture.
وليس المعماريّات فحسب
Their craftsmanship, among other things, is also inferior to ours.
مهاراتهم الحِرفيّة، وأشياء أخرى، أقلّ مستوى من مهاراتنا
Yeah, because we have not only Kaijin and his buddies,
،أجل، لأنّنا لا نملك كايجين ورفاقه فحسب
but Kurobe and Shuna, too.
لدينا كوروبي وشونا أيضاً
But there was just one thing I found absolutely incredible.
لكن ثمّة أمر واحد لاحظتُ بأنّه ممتاز جدّاً
What was it?
ما هو؟
Their agriculture.
الزّراعة لديهم
Their vast fields are unlike anything we have here in Tempest,
حقولهم الواسعة مختلفة تماماً عمّا ،لدينا هنا في تيمبيست
and they grow a brilliant array of produce in abundance.
وينمو فيها نتاجٌ هائل ووفير
Do you think we can learn their techniques?
أتعتقد أننا نستطيع تعلّم تقنيّاتهم؟
I think it's possible.
هذا ممكن باعتقادي
All right!
!حسناً
We'll have our next delegation focus on checking out their agriculture!
!سندع وفدنا التّالي يركّز على تفقّد زراعتهم
We have improved our food situation significantly as it is,
،حسنّا ظرفنا في الغذائيّات بشكل كبير
but in some areas, we are still in a stage of trial and error.
لكن في بعض المطارح، ما زلنا في مرحلة التجربة والخطأ
This may be helpful in improving those areas...
...قد يكون هذا مفيداً في تحسين تلك المطارح
Rigur has grown into such a fine man!
!أصبح ريغور رجلاً حقيقيّاً
Okay, I need to get ready to head for the Dwarf Kingdom,
،حسناً، عليّ أن أستعدّ للتوجّه إلى مملكة الأقزام
so you guys can handle the rest.
لذا يمكنكم تولّي الباقي
I'm counting on you all.
أعتمد عليكم جميعاً
Right!
!حسناً
Great Rimuru.
ريمورو-ساما
If you will allow it,
،لو سمحت
would it be all right to make Rigur the head of the delegation henceforth?
هل سيكون من المناسب تعيين ريغور رئيساً للوفد من الآن فصاعداً؟
What's this about?
ما السّبب؟
I have determined that Demon Lord Carrion can be trusted.
ارتأيتُ أنّ سيّد الشّياطين كاريون شخص موثوق
There is no concern that he will treat our envoys poorly.
ليس هناك قلق من أن يعامل مبعوثينا معاملة سيّئة
That being the case, I feel I should remain here to defend our nation.
بالتّالي، أشعر أنّني ينبغي أن أبقى هنا للدفاع عن بلدنا
Hmm... And you think Rigur can be entrusted to take over.
وتظنّ أنَّ ريغور يمكن الائتمان به لتولّي الأمور
That's what you're saying?
أهذا ما تعنيه؟
Yes.
أجل
Okay, sounds good.
حسناً، فكرة جيّدة
Thank you.
شكراً لك
But if you really trust him that much,
،لكن إن كنت تثق به إلى هذا الحدّ
I guess Carrion rules with more than just strength, huh?
فأعتقد أنَّ كاريون لا يحكم بالقوّة فحسب
Indeed.
بالفعل
The truth is, I tried picking a fight with him,
،في الحقيقة، حاولتُ افتعال شِجار معه
and he laughed at me.
وجعلني سخرية
Huh?!
!ماذا؟
Y-Y-You actually...
...أ-أ-أنت قد
I couldn't use Hell Flare, of course,
،لم أستطع استخدام وهج الجحيم بالطبع
so I lost spectacularly.
لذا خسرتُ خسارة فادحة
I still have much to learn.
ما زلتُ بحاجة لتعلّم الكثير
You're so...
...أنت
Oh, but I did defeat Phobio.
لكن هزمتُ فوبيو
I see...
هكذا إذاً
I mean, it's amazing that you beat Phobio, but...
...أعني، من المذهل أنّك هزمت فوبيو، لكن
Yeah, no! He's definitely a guy I shouldn't have allowed outside this country!
أجل! من المؤكّد أنّني لا ينبغي أن أسمح !لرجل مثله أن يخرج من هذا البلد
So all of that happened, but...
...إذاً حدث كلّ ذلك، لكن
The next day,
،في اليوم الموالي
it was my turn to set off for Dwargon.
كان دوري للانطلاق إلى دوارغون
Hey, Ranga! Too fast!
!رانغا! سريع جداً
Understood, Master!
!عُلم يا مولايّ
Ranga!
!رانغا
This time, I was accompanied by six Goblin Riders, including Gobta and Gobzo...
هذه المرّة، رافقني ستّة من الغوبلن ...بمن فيهم غوبتا وغوبزو
Shuna and Shion...
...شونا وشيون
and Kaijin, along with the Dwarf brothers, Garm, Dord, and Myrd.
وكايجين، مع الأخوة الأقزام غارم ودورد وميرد
It'll be real nice to take it easy in Dwargon again.
سيكون من اللّطيف حقّاً الاسترخاء في دوارغون مجدّداً
I sure do appreciate this.
أقدّر هذا حقّاً
You said it! Right, you guys?
معك حقّ! أليس كذلك يا رجال؟
Absolutely!
!بالتأكيد
I'm glad to hear you guys say that, too.
يسرّني سماعكم تقولون ذلك أيضاً
Our nation has come so far thanks to your help, after all.
وصلت بلدنا إلى ما وصلت إليه بفضل مساعدتكم
Hearing you say that makes me feel blessed to be a craftsman.
سماعك تقول هذا يجعلني أكون ممتنّاً لكوني حِرفيّاً
Yeah.
أجل
I'm truly glad I met all of you.
أنا مسرور حقّاً لأنّني التقيتُ بكم جميعاً
Aw, gee...
...مدهش
By the way, the two carriages behind us
بالمناسبة، العربتان اللّتان خلفنا
are loaded with gifts for King Gazel.
مُحمّلتان بهدايا للملك غازيل
And if you're thinking it would've been easier
وإن كنتم ترون أنّه سيكون من الأسهل
to carry them in my stomach than load them in carriages...
...نقلها بمعدتي أكثر من نقلها بعربات
Formality is important in matters such as these.
الشّكليات مهمّة في مسائل كهذه
...is what I was told.
هذا ما قيل لي...
That's an Ogre princess for you.
هذا ما أتوقّعه من أميرة غيلان
She's been learning a lot from Vesta lately,
،كانت تتعلّم الكثير من فيستا مؤخّراً
so I can count on her when it comes to things like etiquette, too.
لذا يمكنني الاعتماد عليها عندما تتعلّق المسألة بأشياء مثل آداب السّلوك أيضاً
And I thought Shion would be
كما توقّعتُ من شيون
an even worse candidate to let outside the country than Benimaru, but...
مُرشّحة أسوأ من بينيمارو حتّى للسماح ...لها بالخروج من البلد، لكن
What?
ماذا؟
Princess Shuna is going on a vacation with you?
ستخرج الأميرة شونا في إجازة معك؟
No, it's business, not a vacation...
...لا، هذا عمل، لا إجازة
That's not fair! Not fair at all!
!هذا ليس عدلاً! ليس عدلاً على الإطلاق
Why does only Princess Shuna get to have fun with you?!
!لماذا يحقُّ للأميرة شونا فقط أن تستمتع معك؟
It's business! Business!
!هذا عمل! عمل
Lady Shion, please relax!
!شيون-ساما، اهدئي أرجوكِ
Just calm down!
!اهدئي فحسب
So she cried, she screamed, she threw a fit...
...ولذلك بكيت وصرخت واستشاطت غضباً
Can I leave things to you, Rigurd?
هل يمكنني ترك الأمور لك يا ريغورد؟
Th-This is... n-nothing...
...هـ-هذا... سـ-سهل
I felt bad leaving her with Rigurd and the others,
،شفقتُ على ريغورد والآخرين ولم أرد تركها معهم
so I agreed to take her along.
لذا وافقتُ على أخذها معي
Of course, when she's quiet, she looks like a capable lady.
بالطبع، عندما تهدأ، تبدو كسيّدة جديرة
As long as I keep an eye on her, it shouldn't end in disaster.
ما دمتُ أراقبها، لن تقع أي كارثة
Great Rimuru, look.
ريمورو-ساما، انظر
The road that was destroyed in the battle against Charybdis
الطريق الذي دُمِّر في المعركة ضدّ الكاريبديس
is almost completely cleaned up.
رُمِّم تقريباً
Hey, you're right. They work fast.
معكِ حقّ. يعملون بسرعة
Geld and his comrades never cease to impress.
غيلد وزملاؤه لا ينفكّون يدهشوننا
Good. We're on schedule.
جيّد. نسير وفق المخطّط
Sir Geld, we'll need to place an order for more stones.
غيلد-ساما، سنقدّم طلباً لمزيد من الحجارة
Very well.
حسناً
I'll send word to the quarry.
سأرسل طلباً للمقلع
Isn't that...
...أليست هذه
This was the day of your departure for the Dwarf Kingdom?
كان هذا يوم مغادرتك مملكة الأقزام؟
Yeah.
أجل
With the road laid so well, it's been a smooth, easy ride.
بتعبيد الطريق جيّداً، بات طريقاً سهلاً وسلِساً
Yes, we've been working from the direction of the Dwarf Kingdom,
،أجل، كنّا نعمل بدءاً من جهة مملكة الأقزام
so the rest of the road from this point forward is finished.
لذا بقيّة الطريق من هذه النقطة إلى الأمام قد اكتملت
Oh? Sounds like it'll be an even nicer ride from here.
يبدو أنّ الرّحلة ستكون أجمل فأجمل من هنا
Good work!
!أحسنتم عملاً
Thank you.
شكراً لك
So...
...حسناً
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Beer.
بيرة
Beer?!
!بيرة؟
Don't drink too much, though!
!لكن لا تسرفوا كثيراً في الشّرب
Thank you, Great Rimuru!
!شكراً لك يا ريمورو-ساما
Yes, sir!
!حاضر
And so our journey continued smoothly...
...وهكذا استمرّت رحلتنا بيسر
and four days after our departure,
،وبعد أربعة أيّام من مغادرتنا
we arrived in the nation of Dwargon.
وصلنا إلى دولة دوارغون
Gate opening!
!فتح البوّابة
Look at those fine magical beasts pulling their carriages.
انظر إلى تلك الوحوش السحريّة التي تشدّ عرباتهم
Are these people that important?
هل هؤلاء ذوو شأن إلى هذه الدّرجة؟
Those are magical beasts? I've never seen any before.
تلك وحوش سحريّة؟ لم أرَ مثيلاً لها من قبل
The way those carriages are made is unusual...
...طريقة صنع تلك العربات غير مألوفة
Hey, Bro.
يا صاح
Glad to see you're looking so well.
تسرّني رؤيتك بحالة جيّدة
Kaido, it's you!
!كايدو، هذا أنت
It's been so long! How've you been?
لم أرك منذ وقت طويل! كيف حالك؟
I've been having a great time working for Rimuru.
كنتُ أقضي وقتاً عظيماً في خدمة ريمورو
I bet. I can tell from the look on your face.
بالتأكيد. هذا واضح من تعابير وجهك
You guys been doing good, too, Garm?
كنتم تبلون حسناً أيضاً، أليس كذلك يا غارم؟
Yep, thanks for asking.
أجل، شكراً للسؤال
Sure have.
بالتأكيد
So... where's Rimuru, anyway?
إذاً... أين ريمورو على أي حال؟
He's a guest of the state, you know.
فهو ضيف البلد
I need to give him a proper welcome.
أريد أن أرحّب به ترحيباً لائقاً
What's he talking about? I'm right here...
...ما الذي يتحدّث عنه؟ أنا هنا
Oh, right. He only knows my slime form.
تذكّرت. لا يعرفني إلّا بهيئتي الهلاميّة
This is Rimuru.
هذا ريمورو
This is him.
هذا هو
Wha?
ماذا؟
What?!
!ماذا؟
Yeah, some stuff happened...
...أجل، حدثت بعض الأمور
R-Rimuru... sir... you look well, and that's all that matters.
سـ-سيّد... ريمورو... تبدو بخير، وهذا كلّ ما يهمّ
Um... well, then, right this way.
حسناً إذاً، تفضّلوا معي
Yeah, I can't blame him.
أجل، لا ألومه
And so we arrived safely in Dwargon
وهكذا وصلنا بأمان إلى دوارغون
and had our audience with King Gazel right away.
ورتّبنا لقاء مع الملك غازيل فوراً
I'm glad to see you're in good health, Rimuru.
تسعدني رؤيتك بصحّة جيّدة يا ريمورو
Same to you, Dorf-dono.
كذلك أنا يا دورف-دونو
Please, no need for formalities with me.
من فضلك، لا حاجة لمعاملتي برسميّة
Now, our king awaits you.
حسناً، ملكنا ينتظرك
Dorf is the captain of the Pegasus Knights,
،دورف هو قائد فرسان بيغاسوس
who helped us in the battle against Charybdis.
الذي ساعدنا في المعركة ضدّ الكاريبديس
The Pegasus Knights are a top-secret force in direct service to the king,
فرسان بيغاسوس هم قوّة سرّية من النّخبة ،والتي تخدم الملك بشكل مُباشر
so they normally present themselves as regular civil servants, just like this.
لذا يقدّمون أنفسهم عادةً كموظّفين مدنيّين عاديّين بهذا الشّكل
The ruler of the Jura Tempest Federation,
،حاكم اتّحاد جورا تيمبيست
His Majesty Rimuru, has arrived.
جلالته ريمورو، قد وصل
Please, go on inside.
تفضّلوا بالدّخول
The king of the Armed Nation of Dwargon,
ملك الدّولة المُسلّحة دوارغون
Gazel Dwargo.
غازيل دوارغو
It's been some time, Rimuru.
لم أرك منذ وقت يا ريمورو
I see.
هكذا إذاً
Well done.
أحسنت صنعاً
This is quite the intriguing report.
هذا تقرير مثير بحقّ
Thank you.
شكراً لك
I would gladly return your heart to you now...
...سأعيد قلبك بكلّ سرور الآن
but if you would do just one more little job for me,
،لكن ليس قبل أن تؤدّي عملاً بسيطاً آخر لأجلي
it would be a tremendous help.
ستكون مساعدة ذات شأن عظيم
What would you like me to do, Lord Clayman?
ماذا تريدني أن أفعل يا كلايمان-ساما؟
Oh, it's a simple thing, really.
إنّه عمل بسيط حقّاً
Very, very simple.
بسيط جدّاً، جدّاً
Understand,
،أفهمت
Myulan?
يا ميولان؟
Next time, "Paradise, Once More."
"الحلقة القادمة، "الجنّة، من جديد
Paradise, Once More
الجنّة، من جديد